<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research | Shaan Amin</title>
    <link>/research/</link>
      <atom:link href="/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Research</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>©2024</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/logo_huebfbeeb8df50a560f29d39aa9b2eb5b9_334792_300x300_fit_lanczos_2.png</url>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/research/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idea Brokers: Activism By and For Vulnerable Populations in Indonesia</title>
      <link>/research/dissertation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/research/dissertation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My dissertation examines Indonesian activists&amp;rsquo; political attitudes and strategies to conduct public information campaigns and secure rights protections for their vulnerable stakeholders: I use case studies for organizations that work with or for people who are vulnerable (e.g., disabled people, sexual violence survivors). My methodology is pluralist. In my dissertation, I use computational text analysis and discourse analysis to examine diffusion of words and conceptual frameworks across online news platforms, historical legal and policy research to contextualize activists&amp;rsquo; actions, and (most importantly) interviews to understand strategies from the actors working on their behalf. This research was made possible with the support of the National Science Foundation and the Luce Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anticipating Backlash</title>
      <link>/research/framing_bargaining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/research/framing_bargaining/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;How does the anticipation of citizens&amp;rsquo; backlash impact activists&amp;rsquo; lobbying strategies? I model a Markov game between activists and citizens, and find the implication that domestic activists anticipating backlash have incentives to distance from transnational rhetoric pre-emptively. I then examine the case of the anti-sexual violence movement in Indonesia with a combination of historical research, interviews, and text data scraped from &amp;gt;1000 news articles covering a sexual violence prevention bill from 17 major Indonesian news outlets. Despite wide diversity in privately-held preferences, I find homogeneity in activists&amp;rsquo; use of conservative frames and avoidance of feminist frames. Interviews with leadership confirm organizations adopted this strategy to delay and minimize backlash. Press coverage citing left-wing activists is more likely to use words associated with victimhood and less likely to use words associated with feminism than media covering their right-wing counterparts. These counter-intuitive findings suggest that activists&amp;rsquo; caution towards backlash can impact the evolution of discourse on controversial topics within an entire nation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplementary notes and dataset forthcoming upon publication.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
